surfernetwork.com 2019-04-11

# Privacy Policy - SurferNETWORK

##### Personal information

In order to properly respond to an inquiry, we will request of the inquiring party the minimum information to communicate an appropriate reply directly back to that party. 

##### How Personal Data Is Used

  * Communicating with potential publishers who are accessing our site, and in the normal course of business to maintain our products and services
  * Delivering digital content on behalf of our publishers of the audio and video content in order to provide a high quality entertainment experience
  * Measuring and reporting audience statistics and advertising efforts without the ability to identify individuals
  * Otherwise as required by law

###### Data Collected

  * IP address from which a device accesses a client's site or app
  * HTTP user agent

###### Optional Data Collected

  * Name, Email Address, and Phone Number when user uses contact form on website

##### How We Store Data

Personal data is retained only as long as is needed to perform certain Services for our publishers, or as otherwise required by law.

##### Who We Share Data With

Personal data may be shared with the following partners where applicable: demand-side platforms, data management platforms, ad networks, and analytics platforms. 

##### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data that can be sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are often used to track Internet usage. SurferNETWORK uses this technique to allow us to count and keep track of unique listeners using our service, thus fulfilling our counting obligations to broadcasters and advertisers. The technique of counting unique never allows for your identity to be revealed. Advertisers broadcasting via SurferNETWORK may use their own cookies for similar purposes, but in neither case is either party, SurferNETWORK or an advertiser, provided with or allowed access to your personal information. SurferNETWORK uses third party cookies for analytics and reporting data. Should you opt out of cookies, your experience on our site with our publishers may be affected.

##### Third Party Advertising

SurferNETWORK uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may gather information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In tracking you website visits no personal information is collected or provided by or to the advertiser, such as: your name, address, email address or telephone number. If you would like more information about the typical advertising practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

##### SurferNETWORK Technology

Much effort has gone into research and development to provide you the best listening experience on the Internet. Our proprietary software is patented and patent-pending. Our player contains browser capabilities used to display useful information and to take you to popular sites and those consistent with the personalization process. These popular and personalized sites can easily be visited while you are listening to your favorite radio station. You should be aware that other companies' privacy and security policies might differ from ours and you should read the privacy policy of all sites you visit. Unauthorized use of our software is prohibited.

##### Security

We use the best practices in the industry to ensure the security of the services we provide. This includes physical, electronic and managerial safeguards protects the security of personal data provided to us. Our security measures guard against unauthorized access, disclosure, use, change and destruction of data.

##### Nielsen Digital Privacy

Our properties may feature Nielsen's proprietary measurement software which will allow you to contribute to market research, like Nielsen's TV Ratings. To learn more about the information Nielsen's software may collect and your choices with regard to it, please see <http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy>. 

##### Contact

Please contact us at [info@surfernetwork.com](mailto:info@surfernetwork.com) if you have any questions on how data is processed, what data we have for you, or to modify delete or transfer the information.
